我被魔鬼本人折磨过
I've been tortured by the Devil himself.
你能把我怎么样
What can you do to me?
(忆往昔)
她是英国的记录者
She's British Men of Letters.
我们不是一队的吗
Aren't we supposed to be on the same team?
你知道人是可以疼死的吗
Did you know it's possible to die from pain?
别碰我儿子
Get away from my boys.
-妈妈  -没错
- Mom? - ‭Yeah.
妈妈  是猎人
Mom? A hunter?
你原来很厉害  是吧
You were good at this, weren't you?
非常厉害
Very.
猎人  不管多厉害
Hunters... no matter how good they are,
最终结果都是一样的
they all end up the same way.
我从来不希望你和萨姆过这样的生活
I never wanted this for you and Sam.
那孩子的灵质从耳朵流出来了
So the kid had ectoplasm leaking out his ear?
肯定是鬼魂附身
It's gotta be ghost possession.
如果他们够生气
They get angry enough,
就能控制一个人的身体
they can take control of a person's body.
文斯  我们在一起  可以治好你姐姐温蒂
Vince, together, we can heal your sister Wendy.
我们得把路西法关回笼子里
We gotta put Lucifer back in the cage.
而你是唯一做得到的人
You're the only one that can do it.
不是吧
Seriously?
我听说过人死而复生
I've heard of people coming back from the dead before.
但自己活过来  还隔了30年
But to actually do it, after 30 years?
我有好多空白要填补
I just have a lot of blanks to fill in.
对于我  你在这儿就填补了最大的空白
For me, having you here fills in the biggest blank.
(如今)
(莱吉纳)
"没花样了"  开什么玩笑  那地方多棒
"Played out." You're kidding. That place was great.
又是鳄梨吐司  得了吧
Another avocado toast? Please.
是啊  但鳄梨吐司加鹌鹑蛋  真是天才
Yeah, but avocado toast with quail egg? Genius.
你要给他们几颗星
How many stars you giving 'em?
-两颗  -四颗
- Two. - Four.
你知道我们的打分会彼此抵消吧
You realize our ratings are just gonna cancel each other out.
(国会大厦高地  医疗艺术中心  即将开幕)
当初有机会真该买下这里
Should've bought here when we had the chance.
新餐馆  新商店
I mean, new restos, new stores --
价格也变了  这一带都被
New prices. Neighborhood's been picked clean
翻修的和公寓开发商捡干净了
by flippers and condo developers.
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
嗯  从那边房子里传来的
Yeah, it came from that house over there.
是啊  但谁会住在那里啊
Yeah, but who'd want to live in there?
-蹭房的  或者瘾君子  -还带着婴儿
- Squatters or crackheads? - With a baby?
-报警  -什么
- Call 9-1-1. - What?
-快点  -好啦
- Do it! - Okay, okay.
911  请问您有什么紧急情况
9-1-1, what's your emergency?
一座废弃楼房里有个婴儿在哭闹  位置是
Hi, there's a baby in distress in an abandoned house at...
小娜
Nat!
有人吗
Hello?
怎么了
What?
有什么碰了我的胳膊  好像是...
Something touched my arm. I mean, it's something --
-我们得赶紧离开  -好
- We have to get out of here now. - Okay.
[邪恶力量 第12季第3集]
卡西迪奥  你怎么醒了
Castiel. What are you doing here?
我总醒着
Oh, I'm always up.
天使不需要睡觉
Angels don't need sleep.
真希望我有你这毛病
Wish I had that problem.
算了
Anyway...
我再去试试吧
I think I'll go try again.
祝我好运吧
Wish me luck.
好运
Luck.
卡西迪奥
Castiel?
你离开天堂后
After you left heaven,
是什么时候开始觉得
when did it start to feel like...
你融入这里
like you fit, like you...
属于这里
belonged here?
我还不确定我有这种感觉
Well, I'm still not sure I do.
嗯
Yeah.
玛丽
Mary...
你是属于这里的
You do belong here.
晚安  卡西迪奥
Goodnight, Castiel.
好了  你查到女王秘密混蛋团的什么资料了
All right, so what have you found on Her Majesty's Secret Suckbags?
我把地堡翻了个底朝天
Well, I may have turned the bunker upside down
想找到任何提到
looking for any reference whatsoever
英国记录者的东西
to the British Men of Letters,
我只找到了
and all I found
这封塞在一本老账簿里的信
was this letter tucked into an old ledger,
从"伦敦分会"寄来的
from the "London Chapterhouse."
好吧  这算是个发现
Okay, well, that's something.
嗯
Yeah, uh...
也不算是吧
not so much.
真好
Awesome.
早啊  帅哥  来点咖啡
Morning, sunshine. Some coffee?
不了  谢谢  我得走了
No, thank you. I have to go.
-小卡  -小卡  等等
- Cass? - Cass, wait up.
等等
Wait a second.
你去哪
Where you off to?
俄亥俄州  克利夫兰
Cleveland, Ohio.
干什么
For what?
我可能有路西法的线索了
I think I may have a lead on Lucifer.
我找到一份克利夫兰的警方报告
I found a police report in Cleveland
说一名男子眼发红光
about a man whose eyes flared a glowing red.
可能是路西法的新皮囊
It could be Lucifer in a new body.
好吧  听上去有门
All right. Yeah, that sounds like something.
-我们该去看看  -不行
- We should check it out. - No.
魔鬼是因为我才被放出来
The Devil is free because of me.
找到他就是我的责任
Finding him is my responsibility.
小卡  你会需要支援的
Cass, you're gonna want some backup on this.
如果是他  我再打给你们
If it is him, I will call you.
现在  我觉得这里需要你们
In the meantime, I think you're needed here.
那是什么意思
The hell was that about?
妈妈
Mom.
你说什么呢  妈妈好好的
What are you talking about? Mom's fine.
是啊  我昨晚听到她整夜在地堡里走动
Sure. I heard her walking around all night last night.
你不觉得她有点...不爱说话吗
I mean, don't we think she seems a bit...withdrawn?
受了惊吓
You know, shaky?
那是当然的了
Of course she's shaky.
她上次行走人间时
She hasn't been on this planet since
简·方达还穿着护腿呢
Jane Fonda was wearing leg warmers.
她就是需要休息一下
Look, all she needs is a little R&R.
跟家人共处
You know, some good family time...
她就会好起来
she'll be aces.
嗯
Yeah.
早啊
Morning.
我们可以再炸点
Oh, we can fry some more.
估计已经凉了  妈妈
That's -- that's probably cold by now, Mom.
这可是熏肉
It's bacon.
我绝对是你亲生的
We are so related.
你剪头了
Did you cut your hair?
如果要出去猎魔  还是剪短点好
I'm gonna keep it short if I'm gonna go out on a hunt, you know?
干吗留着长发
Why give the bad guys the advantage
让坏人可以拉扯
of long, pullable hair, right?
这话我跟萨姆说了好多年了
I've been trying to tell Sam that for years.
你说  "出去猎魔"
Did you say, uh, "going out on a hunt"?
我发现了个案子
I found a case.
我以为你还在
I thought you were still struggling
摸索互联网这种物呢
with even the idea of the Internet?
迪恩进镇时  我让他买了几份报纸回来
I had Dean pick up some newspapers when he went into town.
我
I...
你可没说你是想找案子
You didn't tell me you were looking for a case.
我没有
I wasn't.
我就是发现了
I just...found one.
明尼苏达州
Minnesota.
两人死亡  房间紧锁
Two dead, locked room.
被害人报警说听到婴儿哭声
Victims had put in a call about a crying baby.
但那里是空的
But the place was empty.
现场只有他们的尸体
The only thing at the scene was their bodies.
已经五天了
Been five days,
验尸官尚未给出死亡原因
and the coroner still hasn't put out a cause of death.
似乎有问题
Seemed fishy.
可能不是案子
It's probably nothing.
我就是想...出去转转
I just thought I might... get out there,
活动筋骨
stretch my legs.
我以为你根本不想去猎魔呢
I-I thought you weren't down to hunt in the first place.
世事多变嘛
Well, things change, right?
家族猎魔之旅
Family hunting trip.
好啊
Sure.
好  10分钟后车里见
All right. Meet at the car in 10.
不是要"休息一下"吗
What about the R&R?
这...
W--
小卡已经治好了你被烤的脚
Look, man, Cass healed your s'mores foot, all right?
宝贝车也被我修复如初  我们可以上路了
I got Baby back to mint. We're road ready.
如果妈妈想猎魔  我们就去
And if Mom wants to hunt, I say we hunt.
你来...
You're gonna...
好摩托
Nice bike.
你走之后  这世上好多东西
There's a lot of things that have gone to seed
都大不如前了
since you were here,
但其中不包括零食的
but the variety in snack food flavors
多变风味
is not one of them.
牛肉干  照烧的  拉差辣椒酱的
We got your teriyaki jerky, we got your sriracha,
辣青柠的  这个
and we got your chili lime, which...
是我的最爱
is my personal favorite.
试试辣青柠的吧
Let's give chili lime a whirl.
不错
It's...good.
人工
Artificial,
有点刺舌头
kinda tingly.
这才叫好
That's how you know it's working.
听着
Look...
我见识过文斯的各种样子
I been around all stripes of Vince, all right?
醉酒的文斯  抑郁的文斯
Drunk Vince, depressed Vince,
夸大狂的"我是金上帝"的文斯
megalomaniacal "I'm a Golden God" Vince.
但把我从门里丢出去的文斯
The Vince who threw me through that door...
那不是他
that wasn't him.
而且不仅是因为他的眼睛
And it wasn't just his eyes, man.
他的力气  他...
I-I mean, the strength. He was like --
就像个综合格斗摔跤手
He was like an MMA fighter.
就像20岁
Hell, he was like 20.
如果你有他的消息
If you hear from him,
一定给我来电
don't hesitate to call.
好的...碧昂斯探员
Okay, Agent...Beyoncé?
那我就是杰斯探员了
I guess that makes me Agent Jay Z.
雪莉·帕特里奇探员  明尼阿波利斯办事处的
Agent Shirley Partridge, out of the Minneapolis field office.
他们是我的搭档  卡西迪和伯纳杜奇探员
These are my partners, Agent Cassidy and Agent Bonaduce.
这是个本地案件
This is a local case.
-联调局为什么会感兴趣...  -他们是新人
- Why would the FBI be interest-- - They're new.
第一次办案想有人指点着
Wanted their first case to have training wheels.
我们想看看尸体
We wanted to have a look at the bodies.
你尚未提交报告
Now, you haven't filed a report.
确认死因出现什么问题了吗
Has there been any problem determining the cause of death?
问题  不不  我查明死因了
Problem? No. No, no, no. I figured out the cause.
只是根本不合理
Just doesn't make any damn sense.
这是烧伤吗
Is this a burn?
冻伤  是啊
Frostbite. Yeah.
两名被害人都死于急性低温
Both victims died of acute hypothermia...
在一间18度的房间里
in a 65-degree room.
我解剖时  他们的心脏都...
When I opened them up, their hearts were literally --
真真正正的  冻住了
and I mean literally -- frozen.
我要怎么把这个告诉公众
Wanna tell me how to present that to the public?
还有他们的家人
Or to their families?
还指点他们呢
So much for training wheels, huh?
偶然相遇  查同一条线索
Bumping into each other, working the same leads.
多巧啊  小卡君
What are the odds, Cassie?
-是命运让我们相遇的  -我不感兴趣
- Fate brought us together. - I'm not interested.
为什么不呢
Why not?
我们组团对付阿玛拉时不挺厉害
We made a somewhat effective team against Amara.
我们都几个月
It's been months, I mean months,
没有试图杀死彼此了
since we last tried to kill each other.
我们都有很强烈的理由
We both got very, very good reasons
希望路西法死
to want Lucifer dead.
再说
Besides...
你跟文斯的二把手交谈时
...while you were gabbing with Vince's second fiddle,
我去翻了他的房间
I was ransacking his room.
发现了这个
Found these.
他亲爱的姐姐温蒂寄来的明信片
Postcards from his beloved sister Wendy.
看啊  地址什么的
Oh, lookie here. An address and everything.
值得一看
Worth a look.
你确定那玩意你会用了吗
You sure you got the swing of that thing?
第三次回答你  会了
For the third time, yes.
迪恩  这不是数码的  我能行
Dean, it's analog. I'm good.
好吧
Right.
妈妈  这里有发现
Mom, we got something over here.
-萨姆  -妈妈
- Sam? - ‭Mom?
迪恩
Dean?
妈妈
Mom? ‭
-妈妈  -萨姆  迪恩
- Mom. - ‭Sam! Dean!
妈妈
Mom!
撑住  妈妈  我们来了
Hold on, Mom! We're coming!
妈妈  离门远点
Mom, get away from the door.
妈妈
Mom.
妈妈  你受伤了
Mom, you're hurt.
走  快走  出去
Let's go. Come on. Come on.
好了
Okay.
可以出去了吗  去挨家敲门
Ready to head out? Go knock on some doors?
-敲门  -是啊
- Doors? - ‭Yeah.
找邻居问问  去记录厅查查
Talk to the neighbors, hit up the Hall of Records,
研究案子
work the...case?
-我们还那么做吧  -有时候吧
- We still do that, right? - Sometimes.
但是  有了互联网  大部分的跑腿工作
But the, uh, the Internet has made a lot of that legwork...
都不必要了
Obsolete.
我已经进入了
I mean, I'm already in
圣保罗的警局数据库
the St. Paul Police Department database.
-有发现吗  -嗯  很多
- Anything? - ‭Yeah, a lot.
查到很多警方报告  有2004年的
I got police reports filed from 2004...
还有91  89  85  78的
uh, '91, '89, '85, '78.
(本地女孩死于肇事逃逸)
都是死亡  都是孩子
All deaths. All kids.
看来一切都始于这个女孩
Looks like it started with this girl here.
伊丽莎白·莫里亚蒂
Elizabeth Moriarty.
你用那个查到了那么多
You got all of that from that.
是啊
Yeah.
妈妈
Mom...
别担心
Don't worry about it.
我们会教你的
We'll teach you how to do this.
你好
Hello.
我是碧昂斯探员
I'm Agent Beyoncé,
这位是我的
and this is my, um...
搭档  斯探员
my partner, Agent Zee.
我们想问你几个问题
Um, we wanted to ask you a few questions
关于你弟...
about your bro...
...弟
...ther.
你觉得萨姆和迪恩也会遇到这种事吗
Do you think that happens to Sam and Dean?
经常的
Oh, all the time.
文尼  打给我
Vinny, please call me.
有两个联邦探员来找你
I got two federal agents asking for you.
不知道你昨天是怎么回事
Don't know what was with you yesterday,
但你惹麻烦了
but you're in trouble.
你说对了  温蒂
How right you are, Wendy.
那么
So...
文斯来过这儿
Vince was here.
昨天来过
Yesterday.
奇怪
Odd.
她最近被人治愈了
She's been recently healed.
是吗
Is that so?
我猜猜  你弟弟让你重新站了起来
Let me guess -- your brother got you up and walking again.
你还喜欢你的双腿吗
And how are you enjoying the use of those legs?
他给你的礼物  我可以拿走
You know, the gift he gave you, I can take away like --
治好你的那东西
The thing that healed you,
不是你弟弟
that wasn't your brother.
是别的东西  古老而邪恶
Something...something else, something old and evil.
我觉得你内心其实是知道的
I...I think a part of you knows that.
我们不想伤害文斯  我们想帮助他
We don't want to hurt Vince. We wanna help him.
他突然跑来
He showed up out of the blue
像奇迹一般治好了我
and he fixed me like a miracle.
但他很冷漠
But he did it cold, like...
仿佛这对他毫无意义
it was nothing to him.
就好像在跑个腿  都没怎么说话
Like he was running an errand. Barely said a word.
然后他跟他的粉丝朋友走了
And then he just took off with his groupie friend.
什么粉丝朋友
His groupie friend?
红发女人  没怎么说话
Red-headed broad. Didn't say much.
文斯在酋长山的小屋
So Vince's cabin in Sagamore Hills...
据说他最棒的专辑都是在那里写的
Apparently, all of his greatest records were written there --
《蛇纹石》《仁慈剧院》
"Serpentine", "Theater of Mercy"...
我早该知道你有事瞒我
I should've known there was something you weren't telling me.
罗威娜
Rowena?
我和妈妈不幸
So mother and I had an unfortunate,
也尴尬地遭遇了路西法
if not rather embarrassing, run-in with Lucifer.
你生气是因为你是我"寻找路西法小队"的
You're just mad because you're only my second choice
第二选择
for a Lucifer-hunt team-up.
不  其实  我觉得这挺温馨
No, actually, I think it's sweet.
我还以为你是受野心和复仇的驱使
I thought your motivation was ambition and revenge,
但现在我知道你只是想救妈妈
but now I know you just wanna save your mother.
才不是为了救她
It's not about saving her.
路西法带着一个法力强大的女巫跑了
Lucifer has made off with a colossally powerful witch
对了  此人还是世间唯一
who, by the way, is the only person alive
能把他关回笼子的人
who can slam him back in the cage.
他要么会杀了她  控制她
He will either kill her, control her,
或者她会提出效力于最大的坏蛋
or she will offer her services to the biggest bad in the town
以求自保  就像她以往那样
in order to save her neck, like she always does.
你觉得这些听上去是好结果吗
Do any of those sound like particularly good outcomes to you?
你那个女巫脑子里
You got any beauty spells locked up
装了什么美容咒吗
in that witchy brain of yours?
我以为这个皮囊能撑久点
Thought this one would last a bit longer
不会像基斯·理查兹老得那么快
before going all Keith Richards on me.
这么跳皮囊我都腻了
This vessel hopping's getting old.
我刚习惯了一具肉身的限制
Just as I get used to the limitations of one meatsack,
就得弃船  再跳进另一具不完美的身体里
I gotta cut bait and jump to the next flawed lump.
你是要我把这具皮囊弄成永久性的吗
Then you want me to make this vessel permanent?
足够强大  能支撑住你
Strong enough to hold you?
是挺合适我的
Does look good on me.
拿出本事来吧  小红
Show me what you got, Red.
我也想帮忙
I-I-I'd help, I would,
但《诅咒之书》不在我手里
but I don't have the Book of the Damned.
我弄丢了
I lost it.
你很清楚你把它放哪了
You know damned well where you put it.
明白我的梗了吗
Did you see what I did there?
"诅咒"
"Damned."
再说  你才不需要那本书
Besides, you don't need the book.
你这么聪明
Clever girl like you
肯定早都记住了
must have it all up here by now.
如果我拒绝呢
And if I refuse?
我就再次扭断你的脖子
I snap your neck again.
但这次
Only this time,
我会直接把你的脑袋扭下来
I'll rip your head clean off afterwards.
-童鬼  -对  来自斯堪的纳维亚传说
- Mylings? - Yeah, from Scandinavian lore.
是儿童的鬼魂  复仇鬼魂
Uh, children's spirits, vengeful ones.
"他们的哭声将大人引向死亡"
"Their cries to help lure adults to their death."
提到冰冻心脏了吗
Anything about frozen hearts?
还没发现
Uh, no, not yet,
但这是古老  不完整的民间传说
but this is just from old, incomplete folk accounts.
我们都知道传说并不是完全准确的
We all know the lore isn't always 100%.
或许吧  但是
Maybe, but...
我只知道  那个抓住了我的小男孩
All I know is, that little boy who grabbed me, I...
他并不想伤害我
He didn't wanna hurt me.
他很害怕
He was scared.
是啊
Yeah, um...
你肯定是那种感觉  但  妈妈
it must've felt that way, but, Mom,
被害人都是被婴儿哭声引去致死的
the victims were all lured to their death by a baby's cry.
娜塔莉亚被杀前  恶灵标记了她
The spirit marked Natalia right before she was killed,
那恶灵也标记了你
the same way the spirit marked you.
要不是我们及时赶了进去
I mean, if we hadn't gotten there in time...
我们知道所有孩子的名字  是吧
Well, look, we know all the kids' names, right?
我们知道他们都葬在本地
We know that they're all buried locally,
我们去撒盐烧骨吧
so I say we salt and burn 'em.
这是个稳妥的办法
That's the safe bet.
同意
Agreed.
好  我们去吧
All right. Well, let's do that.
萨姆
Sammy!
帮帮我
Help me.
妈妈
Mom?
-你没事吧  -妈妈
- Hey, you okay? - ‭Mom?
嗯  没事
Yeah, fine.
我没事  我没事
I'm fine. I'm fine.
我没事
I'm fine.
或许  你该留下
May-- maybe, uh, you should stay here.
给
Here.
-有事打给我们  -好
- Call if you need us. - Okay.
好吧
All right?
就回来
Back soon. ‭
拉姆齐县地契登记簿
Ramsey County Register of Deeds.
你好  我需要张伯伦街1781号
Hello, I'm looking for contact information
最后一位屋主的联系方式  拜托
for the last owner of 1781 Chamberlin Street, please.
好吧  你不能像其他人那样查网站吗
Okay, can't you just use the website like everyone else?
我不是其他人
I'm not everyone else.
拜托了
Please?
谢谢你了
And...thank you.
卢卡斯
Lucas...
他那么冷
was so cold.
我还是不明白是怎么回事
I still don't understand what happened.
我发现他前一分钟才看过他
I checked on him just a minute before I found him.
他怎么会那么快就凉了下来
How'd he get so cold so fast?
天呐  抱歉我这么说个不停
Gosh, sorry for going on like this.
不必道歉
Oh, don't apologize.
卢卡斯什么样
What did Lucas look like?
他好可爱
Well, he was so handsome.
金发  蓝眼睛如水晶一般
Blond hair and these crystal blue eyes.
还有别的吗
Anything else?
他脸颊上有伤疤
He had a scar on his cheek.
邻居的狗弄的
From the neighbors' dog.
谢谢  谢莉尔
Thank you, Cheryl.
很抱歉又提起这些事
I'm sorry for dredging all this up again.
没事的
Oh, it's okay.
其实  也挺好的
Actually, it's kinda nice.
现在都没人打电话了
No one talks on the phone anymore, you know?
我发现了
I've noticed.
再次感谢你
Thank you again.
(卢卡斯·凯林格)
真是可怕的工作
Grim work.
是啊
Yeah.
我担心妈妈
You know, I'm worried about Mom.
为什么
Why?
你不吗
You're not?
她回来了
She's back.
的确  她还在摸索
I mean, yeah, she's still working out the kinks.
我们都是
We're all still working out the kinks.
但是  我们不能就这一次
But, I mean, can't we, for once,
不把什么事都变成个麻烦
just not turn everything into a problem?
我们不能就这一次拥有件美好的东西吗
You know, can we, for once, just have one good thing?
-妈妈不是一件"东西"  -好吧
- Mom's not a thing. - ‭Okay.
迪恩  我也很开心  我开心坏了
Look, I'm happy, too, Dean. I am. I'm overjoyed.
但  她有些不对劲
But...there's something about her.
她有问题
I mean, something's going on with her.
是啊  她在适应
Yeah, she's adjusting.
不  她在挣扎
No, she's struggling.
她想靠埋头猎魔
I mean, she's trying to bury herself in hunting
来避免面对
to avoid dealing.
-你怎么知道  -多年的个人经历
- And how do you know that? - Years of personal experience.
我说不好
I don't know, man. Uh...
有其母必有其子
Like mother, like sons.
妈妈
Mom?
武器袋不见了
Weapons bag is missing.
卢卡斯
Lucas.
你是叫这个吧
That's your name, isn't it?
我跟你妈妈谈了
I talked to your mommy.
她好想你
She misses you so much.
卢卡斯  你为什么带我来这儿
Lucas, why did you bring me here?
帮帮我们
Help...us.
-喂  -妈妈  你在哪
- Hello? - Mom, where are you?
我在张伯伦街的房子
I'm at the Chamberlin house,
查证我的一个预感
on a hunch.
我们把骸骨都撒盐烧毁了
Yeah, we salted and burned all the remains.
那可没起效
Yeah. Didn't work.
从房子里出来  等着我们
Okay, get out of the house and wait for us.
-什么  喂  -妈妈
- What? Hello? - ‭Mom?
喂
Hello?
妈妈
Mom?
快走
Let's go.
山楂树的灰烬
Ash of the Hawthorn Tree.
图案呢
The pattern?
督伊德教的字符
A Druidic glyph.
我用的是我自己发明的混合咒
I'm using a hybrid spell of my own devise --
《诅咒之书》加凯尔特魔法
Book of the Damned and Celtic magic.
应该能让你的皮囊
Should give your vessel
拥有最强大的树的恢复力和强度
the resiliency and strength of the mightiest tree.
按说可以开个黄色笑话
There's a woody joke in there somewhere.
我们说说那个讨厌的词  "应该能"
Let's get back to that nagging little word -- "should."
这种事没人尝试过
It's uncharted territory.
我不能保证咒语会永远有效
I-I can't promise the spell with last forever.
没有已知的这样的魔法
There's no known magic for that.
但它撑得住的
But it will last.
最后一步
The final step.
可以说话吗  黑暗魔王
Permission to speak, Dark Lord?
如果...等咒语成功
If -- when the spell succeeds
你也恢复了全部力量
and you are restored to your full glory...
我会杀了你吗
Will I just kill you?
除了咒语  我还有其他价值
I can be of value beyond this spell.
走着瞧吧
We'll see.
谢谢  陛下
Thank you, my Liege.
[咒语]
小红  你做了什么
Red, what did you do?
加速了腐败  陛下
Sped up the decaying process, my Lord.
你以为基斯·理查兹(摇滚乐手)算够糟了
You thought Keith Richards was bad?
试试伊基·波普
Try Iggy Pop.
砍头
Decapitation is...
都太便宜你了  红发贱人
far too merciful for you, Ginger Bitch!
不
No!
-你休想毁掉我  -现在还不行
- You can't destroy me! - ‭Not yet,
但我可以送你去很远的地方
but I can send you far, far away.
去海底找新皮囊吧
Try finding a new vessel at the bottom of the bloody ocean.
[咒语]
是什么把你困在这里
What's keeping you here?
他
Him.
你是那小女孩的父亲
You're the father of that little girl.
你杀了他们所有人
You killed them all,
所有那些孩子...
all those ch--
妈妈
Mom!
妈妈  来
Mom. Come on.
迪恩
Dean?
她被附身了
She's possessed.
我的家
My house. ‭
我的孩子
My children.
永远是
‭Forever.
妈妈
Mom?
你可以抵抗的
You can fight this.
妈妈
Mom? ‭
‭Mom.
地下室
The basement.
快去
Go!
-妈妈  -妈妈不在了
- Mom? -‭ Mommy's gone.
别  别逼我
Don't. Don't make me.
有我呢  妈妈
I got you, Mom.
如果你们找路西法  他刚走
If you're looking for Lucifer, you just missed him.
喝杯茶吗
Cup of tea?
直到你逼我重新入局
Until you forced me to get back in the game,
我还想忘记路西法来着
I'd tried to forget about Lucifer.
我讨厌他
I loathe him,
我讨厌自己参与了
and I loathe that I had any part
把他从他该待的坑里放出来
in letting him out of the pit he belongs in.
那你会帮我们
So you'll help us, then?
天呐  别做梦了
Good God, no.
联调局西装的打扮
That whole FBI pantsuit look?
我才不喜欢
Not my hex bag.
但如果你们困住了路西法  需要帮助
But if you get Lucifer cornered and find yourself in need,
我会去的
I'm there.
你要洗个澡吗  睡一会儿
Well, you gonna take a shower? Take a nap?
你今天累坏了
You really went through it today.
不  我没事
No, I'm okay.
而且
And, um...
听着  如果我和萨姆
listen, apologies if, uh,
抢了你的活儿或排挤你了  那对不起
me and Sam hijacked or sidelined you in any way.
这是你的案子
I mean, this was your case, you know?
而且你干得漂亮  又一次了
And...well, you kicked ass. Again.
我干得漂亮
I kicked ass?
是你救了我  我...
You saved me. I --
但你是对的
Yeah, but you were right.
那些孩子是无辜的
You know, those kids were innocent.
我们都不知道莫里亚蒂是怎么回事
I mean, hell, we didn't even know what Moriarty's deal was.
我知道
I do.
他附身我时  我看到...
When he possessed me, I saw...
我感觉到了
I felt it.
一切
All of it.
雨果失去孩子后  他疯了
When Hugo lost his child, he went mad.
将自己活埋在了地下室
Buried himself alive in his basement
把自己砌在了墙里  活活饿死
and walled himself in and starved to death.
我去
Damn.
但当新家庭搬了进来
But when new families moved in,
带孩子的家庭
families with children,
他觊觎那些孩子
he coveted those children.
于是便夺走了他们  杀了他们
So he took them. Killed them.
不知怎么将他们的灵魂跟自己的鬼魂连在了一起
And somehow that bound their spirits to his.
他就是这样得到了魔力
What's where he got his power.
他是那么...贪心
He was so...greedy.
扭曲
Twisted.
妈妈  没事了  你回家了
Mom, it's okay. All right? You're home now.
不
No.
我没有
I'm not.
我想约翰
I miss John.
我想我的儿子
I miss my boys.
我们都在  妈妈
We're right here, Mom.
我知道  我明白
I know. In my head.
但我还在哀悼我所认识的他们
But I'm still mourning them as I knew them.
我的新生儿萨姆
My baby Sam.
我的小豆子迪恩
My little boy Dean.
仿佛昨天
Just feels like yesterday,
我们还一起在天堂  而现在
we were together in heaven, and now...
我在这儿  约翰没了
I'm here, and John is gone
他们也没了
and they're gone.
跟你们在一起的每一刻都提醒着我
And every moment I spend with you reminds me
我不能陪伴他们的时光
every moment I lost with them.
我以为如果我猎魔  工作  就能清空思绪
And I thought hunting, working, would clear my head.
妈妈
Mom... ‭
你想说什么
w-what are you trying to say?
我得离开
I have to go.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so...so sorry.
我需要点时间
I just need a little time.
我爱你
I love you.
我爱你们两个
I love you both.